# ARYA YUDHA REYNARDO

+6281293209055 | aryayudhareynardo@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/aryayudhareynardo

Griya Parungpanjang, Tangerang, Banten

I am an Informatics Engineering graduate student with a Web Developer degree. I have various experiences in the world of informatics, especially in the field of building websites. I once worked as a web dev & quality assurance at a PT engaged in the food sector, where I created a website used by the warehouse to select items. In addition, I also have experience in the field of Communications at a Statistics Agency. There, I learned how to communicate with people who need to be more literate about technology to conduct an annual census.

## **Work Experiences**

#### Kuwa Kuwi Cafe - Tangerang, Indonesia

Jul 2022 - Sep 2023

Operation Manager

- Managing customers: Operations managers must ensure customers are comfortable and happy with the cafe's services, including customer service and food and beverage service.
- Manage staff: Operations managers are responsible for recruiting, training, supervising, and motivating their staff to work effectively and efficiently.
- Manage supplies and inventory: An operations manager monitors and manages food and beverage stock, supplies, and other inventory. They must ensure that supplies are always sufficient and in good condition.
- Negotiate with customers who want to reserve a place to make an event.
- Determine the right vendor to apply at Kuwa Kuwi Cafe for customer convenience (selection of internet providers, selection of cashier applications).

### PT. Eden Pangan Indonesia - Jakarta, Indonesia

May 2021 - Jul 2021

Quality Assurant Intern

- Conduct bug searches on the system and propose system improvements to the development team before being used by the warehouse.
- Adding a way to find bugs from only using the manual method added by using the automation method with additional
  applications like katalon

#### PT. Eden Pangan Indonesia - Jakarta, Indonesia

Feb 2021 - Apr 2021

Frontend Web Developer Intern

- Worked with the team to build a system that workers can use in the warehouse to select goods to be prepared for shipment.
- Maintain the system and develop a new UI for the previous design with the team to make it easier to run the applications
  created.

### Badan Pusat Statistik - Tangerang, Indonesia

Apr 2020 - May 2020

Online Cencus Outreach Team Freelance

 Conduct outreach and re-data collection to the community, especially for those with low literacy and technology sensitivity.

## **Education Level**

# Matana University - Tangerang, Indonesia

Aug 2018 - Nov 2022

Bachelor Degree in Informatics Engineering, 3.12/4.00

- · Become a fun coding introduction committee for students visited Matana University with the Matana X-Day theme
- When I was a student at Matana University, I actively participated in several seminars about the world of technology, some of which were "Challenges of computer science in facing the industrial era 4.0"
- Participated in several competitions held on several campuses and the last one was in the top 10 finalists in Course-Net CISC (Computer Scient Innovative Challenge) "Preserving Indonesia Culture"

### **Cerifications & Training**

• Certifications: IT System Analys (October 20, 2021 – 2024) from Badan Pusat Statistik Serfifikasi Profesi